[
  {
    "question": "Which breed has topped the AKC Most Popular Breed list for 30+ consecutive years?",
    "answer": "Labrador Retriever",
    "options": ["Labrador Retriever", "Poodle", "Bulldog"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the only 1934 top five breed that remains in the top five today?",
    "answer": "Beagle",
    "options": ["Poodle", "Border Collie", "Beagle"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which breed's name originates from the word 'Black' signifying the faces of the animals they often tend to?",
    "answer": "Collie",
    "options": ["Collie", "Akita", "Komondor"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which breed won 1st place in AKC's Most Popular Breed list in 2023, usurping the 30+ year champion?",
    "answer": "French Bulldog",
    "options": ["Chihuahua", "French Bulldog", "Golden Retreiver"]
  },
  {
    "question": "While often thought of as Barkless which breed can actually growl and even yodel?",
    "answer": "Basenji",
    "options": ["Basenji", "Great Pyrenees", "Shiba Inu"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In a 1 mile race which breed can outpace a cheetah?",
    "answer": "Greyhound",
    "options": ["Saluki", "Vizsla", "Greyhound"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Whose sense of smell is so accurate that its tracking results can be used in a court of law?",
    "answer": "Bloodhound",
    "options": ["Basset Hound", "Bluetick Coonhound", "Bloodhound"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these breeds is one of only two that has a black tongue?",
    "answer": "Sharpei",
    "options": ["Pomeranian", "Sharpei", "Dalmation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which breed does not actually originate from the country of its name and was developed in the United States?",
    "answer": "Australian Shepherd",
    "options": [
      "Australian Shepherd",
      "German Shepherd",
      "Afghan Hound"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Bred to survive extreme weather conditions which breed has a thick double coat of fur?",
    "answer": "Siberian Husky",
    "options": ["Siberian Husky", "St Bernard", "Great Pyrenees"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which breed of dog was initially bred for Truffle Hunting?",
    "answer": "Lagotto Romagnolos",
    "options": [
      "Brussels Griffon",
      "Lhasa Apsos",
      "Lagotto Romagnolos"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Originally used as herding dogs which of these three breeds has a distinctive corded coat that forms dreadlocks?",
    "answer": "Puli",
    "options": ["Samoyed", "Puli", "Finnish Spitz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which dogs excel in the water and are known for their webbed feet?",
    "answer": "NewFoundland",
    "options": ["Vizsla", "NewFoundland", "Shiba Inu"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Except for a tuft of hair on their head and tail which breed is completely hairless?",
    "answer": "Xoloitzcuintlis",
    "options": ["Bull Terrier", "Azawakh", "Xoloitzcuintlis"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of breed that was originally bred in France as companion dogs and whose name is German for \"little lion.\"",
    "answer": "Lowchen",
    "options": ["Leonberger", "Lowchen", "Hovawart"]
  }
]
